One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
What Death Means
It’s so quiet...
Are they done partying?
Sounds like they stopped
after just one round of drinks.
I didn’t expect Luffy would feel so down...
I need you to take me away
from Egghead-quasar!
It’s true that we failed to
meet our objective, but still...
It’s frustratin’, for sure.
But we had the Five Elders,
a Marine Admiral, CP0, the Seraphim,
and warships surrounding all that!
I’m still tryin’ to wrap my head
around it!
It’s a miracle we even got away
from that total hell, you know?
I absolutely agree with you.
Talk about pathetic...
He’s an Emperor now,
yet he’s mopin’ about one geezer dying.
Oh, c’mon...
All Seraphim to the ship
after recharging!
As for the Sea Beast Weapons
and Pacifista Mk. IIIs...
Rob Lucci! Kaku!
Huh? Where is Stussy?
I killed her.
What?!
What we set out to claim
is now in our hands.
York, Punk Records, the Power Plant...
This puts obtaining the Mother Flame
within our reach.
This will suffice, for now.
However...
We deeply apologize, Sir!
We nine Vice Admirals
led the Buster Call...
But we blundered, allowing the Straw Hats
and Jewelry Bonney to escape!
We’ll proceed to Elbaph from here, Sir!
Do not bother with Elbaph.
If any blunder was committed here,
it was allowing Vegapunk’s broadcast to play.
I never would have imagined...
It is ironic that not only
could we not stop the broadcast,
but that it was the iron giant...
which helped the pirates escape.
Roughly 200 years ago
But St. Saturn!
We were ordered to dispose of it!
Roughly 200 years ago
In the unlikely event they find out,
I will cover for you.
You will study it.
Uh?
That thing is the future.
Researching it will
benefit the military in time.
Thank you, Sir!
We’re deeply interested in it, as well!
Since then, it had not moved even once,
and two hundred years have passed.
But...
it clearly moved
to protect Straw Hat Luffy!
St. Saturn.
I want to ask you something
as a sailor serving the Government.
You called it a “blunder”...
Does that mean...
what Vegapunk said is true?
Vice Admiral Doberman!
I want our medics on their feet, now!
What’s all...?
Island clouds?
Aw, crud!
Why’re there so many?!
Is the Cloud Plant malfunctioning?!
What’s goin’ on?
Oh, I get it!
That you, Edison?!
You didn’t die in the Fabriophase?!
Oops, busted.
Dammit...
He tricked me!
Punk Records...
has been taken away!
Holy
Land
Mary
Geoise
What does this mean-eh?!
Is what Vegapunk said true?!
Where is Akainu?!
How will he answer for Kuma’s mess?!
Even if the world sinks,
it won’t affect the Holy Land, but...
We-We don’t have a lot of food-eh!
Hey, Chef. I asked for beef-eh.
What’s this fish doing here?!
Growwwl
Forgive me, my lord.
We’ve run out...
I’ve never been so...
humiliated-eh!
We’re facing... a severe food shortage!
I reluctantly skipped one meal
and even a snack yesterday!
What?! That’s a diet fit for prisoners!
Famine?! We’ll starve to death!
We must kill the person who is in charge!
We must punish and admonish the peasants!
This is due to their negligence
and mismanagement-eh!
Hall
of
Autho-
rity
Hey! What do you think you’re doing here...
Garling?
I have just received orders...
What orders? Whose?
Care to explain your tone, Garling?
Know your place.
Going forward, Vegapunk York
is to be under my direct command...
and I shall assume the role of
Godhead of Science and Defense.
Impossible!
The world’s entering a time of turmoil...
An unprecedented period of turbulence.
Let us work together to better this world,
my fellow Elders.
Five Elders
St. Figarland Garling
(Godhead of Science & Defense)
St. Saturn, what’s the matter?!
What the hell’s happening?!
Medics! Hurry!
This is terrible! We can’t allow
the world’s highest authority to come to harm!
Sir, have you caught something?
Is there anything we
can do for you, St. Saturn?!
Have I been...?
Great Imu!
I...
Saturn, wherefore hast thou
permitted Joyboy to escape?
mu...
Mercy, please!
I did not know that his powers
were so nebulous!
Great... Imu...
S... St. Saturn?
Bo...
Bones...?
We couldn’t retake the Labophase...
York got in our way! Dammit all!
Our Mental Waves can reach anywhere...
So York still has access here.
Ah getcha, but it’s better than
lettin’ her have da real deal.
Fer now, let’s jus’ watch over dis genius brain of ours
‘til humanity can make proper use of it.
That will take five centuries. Did you make
these island clouds the floating type?
O’ course! Far’s the world’s concerned,
Vegapunk’s dead ‘n gone!
We can go globetrottin’ all we want!
We can’t create inventions because we have
neither the funds nor the materials...
We’ll look to our friends fer dat.
‘Kay, den!
Ta- daah!
Howzat?
You look so ridiculous!
Were you hoping to have
a body type like mine?
Y’all talkin’ outta yer butts!
Toss out York’s body parts!
Good call! Dey’s bad vibes!
Hello? Is this Weatheria?
This is Vegapunk!
What?! What do you want?!
I thought you were dead!
Oh, I don’t like this!
Hey, what’s gonna happen now?
Are we gonna die?!
I don’t wanna die!
Kama-
bakka
Queen-
dom
I choose life! I’ll swim to live!
So, basically...
a massive war occurred
during the undocumented Void Century,
and the Ancient Weapons
used in that conflict...
caused the world to sink
by 200 meters.
Whoever claims the One Piece and
becomes the King of the Pirates...
will have that power once again!
We can’t just wait for that to happen.
The world sinking into the sea...
The fact that the Celestial Dragons reside
at the world’s highest elevation, the Red Line...
Tequila Wolf.
Tequila Wolf
Vodka Wolf
Vodka Wolf.
Rum Wolf
Rum Wolf.
Bourbon Wolf
Bourbon Wolf.
All of those megastructures
that they’ve had slaves constructing,
going back 700 years!
Yeah...
Yeah, it all starts to make sense.
I was gonna say that!
Oh, I don’t like this!
Vegapunk...
Unfortunately, not all who believed
the words you gave your life to share...
will prepare for
the looming disaster peacefully.
Don’t lose sight of
your target now, Dragon.
This demands a swift resolution.
Otherwise...
people will start fighting
over the safe areas that remain.
She woke up!
Huh...
I...
Whew, what a relief!
You feeling okay, Lilith?
Lilith!
Lilith...
All that said, you’re in a cabin
on the giants’ ship.
Everything’s huge here.
The giants...
Lilith, the thing is...
I hate to say this,
but we failed to get
any other Vegapunks out besides you.
I’m so sorry.
Atlas was the one who knocked you out,
but I think she did it in order to...
It’s fine. I know.
I’ve just been informed of everything.
“Just been informed”? By who?
Just give me a minute to cry.
What about you is evil, exactly?
I’m hungry!
You recover quick!
Well, then... If you’re hungry,
the giants set out fruit for us on the table.
Come over once you’ve calmed down.
I’ll wait for you there.
Now...
why am I getting so hungry?
Oh!
Must be because my brain’s
no longer linked with York’s.
Good to see you, Lilith!
I see you’ve come to!
Is the grub up there?
“Grub”?
Oh, you mean food.
It’s rather depressing up there...
Sulk
Oh? Why’s that?
Damm ih! Ah promished ‘im...
Are you okay?
Oh, Lilith... Luffy’s really
down about it, too.
He’s so depressed,
he’s losing his appetite...
I promised Apple Gramps
I’d help ‘im escape...
Gramps...!
He’s only eaten
five bunches of grapes...
He’s had plenty!
I see... That’s why you’re depressed.
But don’t be!
I’ve just been informed...
“Just”?
You keep telling us you’ve “been informed”.
What do you mean by that?
The reason I cried earlier is because
I’m saddened by everyone’s deaths.
But that’s only according to
your definition of death.
The truth is, simply put...
They’re all alive!
WHAAAA?!
But to you, they’re dead!
Nope, don’t get it!
You mean they’re ghosts?
Horrifying!
Rich, comin’ from you!
What I’m trying to say...
is that you guys kept your word!
So...
don’t be so down, Luffy!
I don’t really get it, but...
you mean Apple Gramps is still there?
Yup, sure is!
Quit asking what’s real and what’s not!
You decide for yourself!
If you ask me, that concept
is just a relic of the past!
I get it... The gramps
and the others’re there...
I get it!
Hey, Luffy!
Straw Hat!
You feeling better now?!
Hey, giant guys!
Thanks for coming to save us!
Sure thing! So you wanna kick it off now?!
Wanna feast?!
Yeah!
So this is how these brave warriors feast!
Hey, Zoro! Luffy’s...!
Get over here, everybody!
Been waitin’ for you all!
Eat all you like!
Hey, hold up, wait!
I knew the giants’ food would be huge!
Food!
Let’s dig in!
Yummy!
Once we get to Elbaph,
we’ll treat you to some real tasty food!
There’s plenty more...
in Elbaph!
Once we land at Elbaph...!
Robin! There’s tons of
tasty food to go around!
In Elbaph, we’ve got...
Once we get to Elbaph,
I can see Saul!
Good for you, Robin!
Vegapunk said whoever finds the One Piece
controls the world!
Who do you think’s
gonna be the King of the Pirates, then?
Hey! That’s why I...
set out to sea!
Straw Hat!
Forget about the toast earlier!
Let’s have a redo!
Even if you all turn against me...
you know it’s gonna be me!
Cheers!
Nika?
That’s right, he’s my hero.
He’ll come laughing,
moving to this rhythm:
Daddy...
I know my daddy’s the kindest,
most wonderful person
in the whole world!
And I’ll never, ever forget it!
The next time we see each other, we’ll be
out on the waters, watching the horizon together.
We finally got to see it together!
The horizon!
The ship’s course is set, sailing resolutely
to the northeast,
making her way to Elbaph,
the long-awaited country of the giants.
New World
Warland, Elbaph
Come on...
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
piipapii papipo, piipapii
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
no no no no no norenai
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama feel so good, mata unlucky demo
cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no boys & girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no boys & girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran run run run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga punk!!!!!! no way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamine
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru